{
    "id": "5ad36717ba8c4aeca4235a8206103fe6",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise (Passive Voice)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The prizes ……………………………… away by the chief guest.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "gave",
                "were giving",
                "were given"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dc51b7f064c547dcb657f0f88e38d4fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ……………………….. from drowning.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "rescued",
                "has rescued",
                "was rescued"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "335fc340c48343de86e86ffcdff82cdf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The match …………………………..",
            "description": "In the present perfect, the passive form is made with has/have + been + ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "has cancelled",
                "has been cancelled",
                "has been cancelling"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60280f70a1aa43058dc3a24e473ab879"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy …………………………… to stand outside the class for an hour.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has made",
                "was made",
                "has been made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "288b6c8e9d3145cd92a23dc37781b7fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ……………………………. by a snake.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has bitten",
                "was bitten",
                "was biting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc777e846d2544349a864833a4cd0687"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dinner is ready …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to serve",
                "to be served"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d044685aa154e4c82b8dcc99e8a5f63"
        },
        {
            "question": "Messengers ……………………….. to different parts of the country.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "were sending",
                "have sent",
                "were sent"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4fdd1b00682d4b34915544c745f98a0b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. for his alcoholic addiction.",
            "description": "In the present continuous tense, the passive form is made with is/are/am + being + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is treating",
                "is being treated",
                "has been treating"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "756a03682c6d412c8ef3ba7a88fa91e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ……………………………. with a cane.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "was beating",
                "has beaten",
                "was beaten"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "97f98fcd0e7144cfa06e411805b2be37"
        },
        {
            "question": "The case ……………………………. by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is investigating",
                "is been investigated",
                "is being investigated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a5d4ae5c71f34fe8bf4c9287467a7419"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hindi ………………………….. in much of North India.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is spoken",
                "has spoken",
                "is speaking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6d329dd1abc141ec9e0a33ddf6ca36ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………. of the consequences.",
            "description": "In the present perfect, the passive form is made with has/have + been + ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "are warning",
                "have been warned",
                "have warned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a21ebfd2c1d04ca7a3b80d2abd68117f"
        }
    ]
}